Guide to the Stanford University, Stanford Repertory Theatre, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Stanford Repertory Theatre, records
1965-1970
SC0114
Stanford University. Stanford Repertory Theatre.
16.5 Linear feet
These records cover the whole period of SRT's operations and include correspondence, graphics, photographs, production books and scrapbooks of publicity clippings.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Department of Drama, 1973.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford Repertory Theatre (SRT) represented an attempt to establish a professional repertory theatre on the Stanford campus. Originally funded by the Rockefeller Foundation with a matching grant from the University, it was phased out at the end of the grant as an unsuccessful and expensive project.
Description of the Collection
These records cover the whole period of SRT's operations and include correspondence, graphics, photographs, production books and scrapbooks of publicity clippings.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Department of Drama.; Stanford University. Stanford Repertory Theatre.; College and school drama, American--California--Stanford.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Business Files
    Box 1 Contains correspondence and records on various professional affiliations (ANTA, Ford Foundation), insurance policy transactions, mailing lists, ticket orders, box office reports and annual budgets for 1965 through 1969.
    Box 2 Contains subscription reports and records, box office reports by individual production, and salary/tax/payroll personnel forms.
    Box 3 Contains group ticket orders and sales records, mailing lists (groups, industrial groups, and individuals), newsletters, news releases, ticket information, correspondence with ticket agencies, and correspondence-transactions with Actors Equity.
    - "A" (Box 1)
    - Anta (Box 1)
    - Addressing Equipment (Box 1)
    - American Educational Theater Ass'n (Box 1)
    - Arts Management (Box 1)
    - ASSU (Box 1)
    - Acting Fellows (Box 1)
    - "B" (Box 1)
    - Steve A. Baffrey (Box 1)
    - Bank of Calif Calendar (Box 1)
    - CAPA (Box 1)
    - "C" (Box 1)
    - Calendar Sheets (Box 1)
    - Computicket (Box 1)
    - "D" (Box 1)
    - Dramatist's Play Service (Box 1)
    - "E" (Box 1)
    - Employee Benefits (Box 1)
    - Executive Committee (Box 1)
    - "F" (Box 1)
    - Film-Spot Announcement (Box 1)
    - Final Exam-Theater Management Speech and Drama 245 (Box 1)
    - The Ford Foundation (Box 1)
    - "G" (Box 1)
    - Guarnateers and Warranties (Box 1)
    - "H" (Box 1)
    - "I" (Box 1)
    - Insurance (Box 1)
    - Insurance - Prop Loan Forms (Box 1)
    - "J' (Box 1)
    - Job Descriptions (Box 1)
    - "K" (Box 1)
    - "L" (Box 1)
    - Library Collection (Theaters) (Box 1)
    - "M" (Box 1)
    - MFA Program (Box 1)
    - Mailing Information (Box 1)
    - Manuscripts Returned, Jun 1970 (Box 1)
    - Maps-Stanford, other (Box 1)
    - Meidel Room (Box 1)
    - Misc. (Box 1)
    - "N" (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts-National Council on the Arts (Box 1)
    - News Articles and periodical items of personal interest. (Box 1)
    - Nothwest Drama Conference Tour-College of Marin (Box 1)
    - "O" (Box 1)
    - Office Machines (Box 1)
    - "P" (Box 1)
    - Personnel, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Personnel (Box 1)
    - Personnel List: SRT' VS, MFA, Faculty etc. (Box 1)
    - Postage Meter (Box 1)
    - Publication and Theater Information (Box 1)
    - "Q" (Box 1)
    - Quarterly Reports-SRT (Box 1)
    - Rockefeller Grant (Box 1)
    - "R" (Box 1)
    - SRT-Background and History (Box 1)
    - SRT-General Info -1966-67; Financial, Policies, Personnel (Box 1)
    - "S" (Box 1)
    - Schools, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Speech and Drama (Box 1)
    - "T" (Box 1)
    - New Theater Planning (Box 1)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Theater World (Box 1)
    - SRT Tour Shows (Box 1)
    - Tulane Drama Review (Box 1)
    - "U" (Box 1)
    - "V" (Box 1)
    - "W" (Box 1)
    - "XYZ" (Box 1)
    - Budget, 1965-66 (Box 1)
    - Budget, 1966-67 (Box 1)
    - Budget, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Budget, 1968-69 (Box 1)
    - Financial Reports, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Financial Reports, 1968-69 (Box 1)
    - Financial Reports, 1969-70 (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - The Iceman Cometh (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - The Wager (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - The Cage (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - Androcles and the Lion (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - Drums of Snow (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - Waiting for Godot (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - The Winter's Tale (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - Shadows of Heroes (Box 1)
    - Box Office Report - Unknown soldier and his Wife (Box 1)
    - House Manager's Reports, 1969-70 (Box 1)
    - Out Rep and High School Program, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Previews and Audience Briefings; Discussions, 1967-68 (Box 1)
    - Workshop-Jew of Malta (Box 1)
    - Workshop-Andromache (Box 1)
    - Workshop - Cock-A-Doodle Dandy (Box 1)
    - Ticket Orders, 1969-70 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-67 (Box 2)
    - Various - Stanford Players (Box 2)
    - "Troilus and Cressida", Summer 1970 (Box 2)
    - Daily Sales Reports, 1969-70 (Box 2)
    - Box Office Summeries, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Box Office Reports, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Reports, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Cash Receipts, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - House Manager Report, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Daily SaIes Reports, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Budget, 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Daily Sales Reports, 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - House Manager Report, 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Reports, 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Ticket Inventory (Box 2)
    - Chekhow and Hard Rock Box Office (Box 2)
    - The New Tenant Box Office (Box 2)
    - The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window Box Office (Box 2)
    - The Cavern Box Office (Box 2)
    - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance Box Office (Box 2)
    - Inspector General Box Office (Box 2)
    - A Pair of Aces Box Office (Box 2)
    - UBU REX Box Office (Box 2)
    - Candaules, Commissioner Box Office (Box 2)
    - Cock-A-Doodle Dandy Box Office (Box 2)
    - The Man Behind the Mask Box Office (Box 2)
    - Out at Sea and Meeting Place Box Office (Box 2)
    - Box Office Reports, 1966-67 (Box 2)
    - Budget - Financial Reports, 1966-67 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Only - Deposits, 1966-67 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Reports, 1966-67 (Box 2)
    - Budget - Financial Reports, 1965-66 (Box 2)
    - Tax (Box 2)
    - Government Funds/Subsidy (Box 2)
    - Season Tickets, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Season Tickets, 1953-54 (Box 2)
    - Subscription Season, 1951-52 (Box 2)
    - Season Ticket, 1948-49 (Box 2)
    - Acting Fellowships 1968-69 C. Gantner and C. EdeIman (Box 2)
    - Appointment letters, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Appointment notices- monthly. SU-1., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Change of status. SU-2., 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Change in status. SU-2., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Employment and change notice. SU-7., 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Employment and change notice. SU-7., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Hours worked record. SU-27. (Box 2)
    - Leave of absence or termination notice. SU-3., 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Leave of absence or termination notice. SU-3., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Overtime and misc. payment authorizations. SU-4., 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Overtime sheets, 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Special salary processing request. SU-31., 1967-68 (Box 2)
    - Special salary requests. SU-31., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Withholding tax and payroll data. SU-32., 1966-68 (Box 2)
    - Withholding tax and payroll data. SU-32., 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - WORK-STUDY RECORDS AND INFORMATION (Box 2)
      - Payroll processing - information. Effective May 1969., 25324 (Box 2)
      - Hours worked record, work-study employees. SU-27., 1968-69 (Box 2)
      - Time sheets, work-study, 1968-69 (Box 2)
      - Payroll forms, work-study (Box 2)
      - Semi-monthly time sheets, 1968-69 (Box 2)
      - Work-study, summer, 1970 (Box 2)
      - Work-study, procedures, 1970-71 (Box 2)
      - Payroll correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 2)
      - Non-equity extension contract (Box 2)
      - Equity payroll forms (Box 2)
      - Non-professional affidavits (Box 2)
      - New York unemployment, 1966-68 (Box 2)
      - Actor's Equity Association contracts (Box 2)
    - Backstage night. (Box 3)
    - Club presidents - Alumni and others. (Box 3)
    - Community Association for Retarded - group sale. (Box 3)
    - Forms - box office receipts., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Group ticket form., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Loan forms., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Forms - performance box office reports. (Box 3)
    - Group ticket purchases., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Group ticket orders., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Group orders - playgoer's workshop. (cancelled), 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Group sales., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Group sales (Box 3)
    - High school workshop - mailing list., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - High school workshop - mailing list and response., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - High school press conference - mailing list., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - High school volunteers. (Box 3)
    - Labels. (Box 3)
    - Mailing list - industry. (Box 3)
    - SRT volunteer mailing list. (Box 3)
    - Memphis report and masters. (Box 3)
    - Ming's luncheon - mailing list., 1969 (Box 3)
    - Resumes., 1970-72 (Box 3)
    - SRT volunteer newsletters. (Box 3)
    - News release and radio-T.V. release directory. (Box 3)
    - Out-rep., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Out-rep appreciation letters. (Box 3)
    - Original study of posters. (Box 3)
    - Quarterly reports. (Box 3)
    - Requested program forms., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - SRTV membership list., 1969 (Box 3)
    - Work of other volunteer groups. (Box 3)
    - Press releases., 1965-67 (Box 3)
    - Refund note. (Box 3)
    - Ticket prices., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Ticket prices., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Ticket prices., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Ticket printing., 1966 (Box 3)
    - Ticket orders., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Ticket orders., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Ticket agencies. (Box 3)
    - Ticket agencies., 1966-67 (Box 3)
    - News releases., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - News releases., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Press releases., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Resumes., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - News release directory. (Box 3)
    - Press releases., 1966-67 (Box 3)
    - Daily sales reports. (1), 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Daily sales reports. (2), 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Work-study withholding forms. SU- 32., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Equity information. (Box 3)
    - Equity - sample contracts. (Box 3)
    - Equity policies - students. (Box 3)
    - Equity contracts., 1969-70 (Box 3)
    - Equity - league contracts., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Equity contracts., 1968-69 (Box 3)
    - Actor's Equity Association - correspondence., 1967-68 (Box 3)
    - Equity - miscellaneous. (Box 3)
    - Equity - non-professional affidavits. (Box 3)
    - Equity - correspondence., 1966-67 (Box 3)
    - Equity - unemployment insurance. (Box 3)
    - Equity - contract correspondence., 1966-67 (Box 3)
    - Equity - double residence. (Box 3)
    - Equity - welfare and pension. (Box 3)
    - Equity - deputy and actor memos. (Box 3)
    - Equity - insurance forms and regulations. (Box 3)
    - Equity - correspondence., 1965-66 (Box 3)
    - Equity - file with AEA contract., 1965-66 (Box 3)
    - Equity - payroll approvals. (Box 3)
    - Equity - various forms and regulations. (Box 3)
    - Equity foundation - dept. to extend professional theater. (Box 3)
    - Equity contracts - signed., 1965-66 (Box 3)
    - Form contracts., 1966-67 (Box 3)
    - Non-professional affidavit. (Box 3)
    - Non-professional affidavit. (Box 3)
    - Equity overtime agreement. (Box 3)
  - Personnel Files (Box 4)
    Contains personnel files by individual employee, in alphabetical order. Actors' and actresses' files include professional resumes and photos (Head Shots).
    - Androsky, Carol (Box 4)
    - Barry, Michael (Box 4)
    - Book, Stephen Jay (Box 4)
    - Box office personnnel. (Box 4)
    - Brown, Barbara (Box 4)
    - Burgess, Judith (Box 4)
    - Cannon, Glen (Box 4)
    - Cason, Barbara (Box 4)
    - Devrim, Sirin (Box 4)
    - Feldner, Sheldon (Box 4)
    - Gantner, Carrillo (Box 4)
    - Gay, Errol (Box 4)
    - Gerety, Anne (Box 4)
    - Gould, Harold (Box 4)
    - Green, Gilbert (Box 4)
    - Hoffman, Jane (Box 4)
    - Halwer, Amy V. (Box 4)
    - Heafele, Jenny (Box 4)
    - Hay, Dick (Box 4)
    - Hiken, Barbara (Box 4)
    - Hiken, Gerald (Box 4)
    - Holsinger, Sherry (Box 4)
    - Hornbacher, Jay Paul (Box 4)
    - Huddle, Elizabeth (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Derek (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Dorothy (Box 4)
    - Hunt, Ruth (Box 4)
    - Israel, Irving (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Doug (Box 4)
    - Karlen, John (Box 4)
    - Kennedy, Steven L. (Box 4)
    - Landry, Paul (Box 4)
    - Langinieux, Michel (Box 4)
    - Leich, Sue (Box 4)
    - Leversee, Loretta (Box 4)
    - Lindsey, Gary (Box 4)
    - Lovelady, Bruce (Box 4)
    - Loper, Robert B. (Box 4)
    - Lyon, Nyla Sharon (Box 4)
    - McFarland, Robert (Box 4)
    - McComas, Maggie (Box 4)
    - McDermott, Gaila E. (Box 4)
    - Medalis, Joe (Box 4)
    - Muffatti, S. Todd (Box 4)
    - Newman, Stephen D. (Box 4)
    - Norman, Maide (Box 4)
    - Nyberg, Elizabeth (Box 4)
    - Olson, Charles (Box 4)
    - Parone, Edward (Box 4)
    - Paynter, Jeanne (Box 4)
    - Parker, Carolyn (Box 4)
    - Personnel information forms (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 4)
    - Raphel, Jerome (Box 4)
    - Russel, Douglas (Box 4)
    - Richards, Paul E. (Box 4)
    - Rebillot, Paul (Box 4)
    - Reisman, Jane (Box 4)
    - Reynolds, Edgar (Box 4)
    - Randall, Juliet (Box 4)
    - Runyon, Barbara (Box 4)
    - Schacht, Sam (Box 4)
    - Scott, Joseph (Box 4)
    - Shapiro, Melvin (Box 4)
    - Sears, Dean Robert R. (Box 4)
    - Silveira, Ruth (Box 4)
    - Stern, Morgan (Box 4)
    - Sharp, Bill (Box 4)
    - Troxell, Peter B. (Box 4)
    - Vos, Erik (Box 4)
    - Waggoner, Rex (Box 4)
    - Winfield, Paul (Box 4)
    - Willsrud, Astrid (Box 4)
    - Wright, John (Box 4)
    - GENERAL PERSONNEL (Box 4)
      - Employment questionaire. (Box 4)
      - Personnel., 1965-66 (Box 4)
      - ASM (Box 4)
      - Personnel employed. (Box 4)
      - Office personnel. (Box 4)
      - Resumes. (Box 4)
  - Individual Production Files
    Box 5 Files contain primarily correspondence about particular production, also business forms, records, and some advertising relating only to a particular production. Box 6 Files contain photographs (in print and contact sheet form) of individual productions.
    - 1969-70 (Box 5)
      - Season, 1969-70. (Box 5)
      - The Drums of Snow (Box 5)
      - Androcles and the Lion (Box 5)
      - The Iceman Cometh (Box 5)
      - Press conference - Androcles., Nov 24, 1969 (Box 5)
      - The Cage (Box 5)
      - The Wager (Box 5)
      - Shadow of Heroes (Box 5)
      - Unknown Soldier and His Wife (Box 5)
      - The Winter's Tale (Box 5)
      - Out-rep. (Box 5)
      - Theater sale. (Box 5)
      - Waiting for Godot (Box 5)
      - Class projects. (Box 5)
    - 1968-69 (Box 5)
      - Andromache (Box 5)
      - Blood Wedding (Box 5)
      - The Queen and the Rebels (Box 5)
      - The Jew of Malta (Box 5)
      - Royalties - student projects. (Box 5)
      - The Cuchulain Cycle (Box 5)
      - Feast of Cuchulain (Box 5)
      - Learned Ladies (Box 5)
      - Spring plays., 1969 (Box 5)
      - Royalties. (Box 5)
      - The Virtues of Adultery and The Silhouette of God (Box 5)
      - The Creditors and The Window - Mfa projects, fall quarter. (Box 5)
      - The Birthday Party (Box 5)
      - Theater of the Congressional Record - election by the House of Representatives, 1825. (Box 5)
    - 1967-68 (Box 5)
      - Advertising. (Box 5)
      - General, 1967-68. (Box 5)
      - The Cavern (Box 5)
      - Canduales, Commissioner (Box 5)
      - Cock a Doodle Dandy by Sean O'Casey (Box 5)
      - The Inspector General (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Chekhov one acts - Proposal/The Boor/Swan Song (Box 5)
      - Out at Sea (Box 5)
      - Pound on Demand and Hello Out There by Samuel French (Box 5)
      - Out at Sea (Box 5)
      - Copyright correspondence - There is a Meetong Place (Box 5)
      - Serjeant Musgrave (Box 5)
      - A Mans a Man (Box 5)
      - Ubu Rex (Box 5)
      - There is a Meeting Place - Correspondence file. (Box 5)
      - Contemplated plays - 1967-68 season. (Box 5)
      - Theater of Congressional Record (Box 5)
      - Unwicked Witch (Box 5)
    - 1966-67 (Box 5)
      - Wank, Williams and Neylan - general. (Box 5)
      - Advertising - pre-season. (Box 5)
      - General royalties. (Box 5)
      - Antony and Cleo - advertising. (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Antony and Cleo. (Box 5)
      - Beggar's Opera advertising. (Box 5)
      - Cherry Orchard advertising. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Cherry Orchard. (Box 5)
      - Promotion - The Cherry Orchard. (Box 5)
      - Once in a Lifetime - advertising. (Box 5)
      - Once in a Lifetime - royalties. (Box 5)
      - Once in a Lifetime (Box 5)
      - Inadmissible Evidence advertising. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Inadmissible Evidence. (Box 5)
      - One act advertising. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - A Slight Ache. (Box 5)
    - 1965-66 (Box 5)
      - Promotion. (Box 5)
      - Scapin advertising. (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Scapin. (Box 5)
      - Scapin (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Skin of Our Teeth. (Box 5)
      - Skin Advertising. (Box 5)
      - Skin of Our Teeth (Box 5)
      - Prometheus Bound advertising. (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Prometheus Bound. (Box 5)
      - Prometheus (Box 5)
      - Prometheus Bound general. (Box 5)
      - All's Well promotion. (Box 5)
      - All's Well advertising. (Box 5)
      - All's Well - general. (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Goodwoman. (Box 5)
      - Good Woman advertising. (Box 5)
      - Goodwoman of Setzuan (Box 5)
      - Promotion - Chairs and Questions. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Questions. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Chairs. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Visit. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Public Eye. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Diary of a Madman. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Physicists. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Marat/Sade. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Gnadiges Fraulein. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Hundred and First. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - The Lover. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Meteor. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - A Moon for the Misbegotten. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Oh What a Lovely War. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Old Glory. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Oppenheimer. (Box 5)
      - Royalties - Plebeians Rehearse the Revolution. (Box 5)
    - Season poster., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - Andromache., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - The Queen and the Rebels., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - The Mafia Sings., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - The Window and The Creditors., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - Cuchulain., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - The Jew of Malta., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - Blood Wedding., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - Ajax 69., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - Season., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum., 1968-69 (Box 5)
    - The Cavern., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - The Inspector General., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Cock-A Doodle Dandy., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Theater of Congressional Record., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Canduales, Commissioner., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous., 1967-68 (Box 5)
    - Season., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - Antony and Cleopatra., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - Inadmissible Evidence., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - Out at Sea: There is a Meeting Place., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - Once in a Lifetime., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - The Cherry Orchard., 1966-67 (Box 5)
    - THE CAVERN - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - PHOTOS - Loveliest Day of the Year, SRT Volunteers (Box 6)
    - PHOTOS - Iceman Cometh (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - Androcles (Box 6)
    - ANDROMACHE (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - Learned Ladies & Naked (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - Queen & Rebels (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - UNKNOWN SOLDIER (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - Costume Dept. (Box 6)
    - (P.A. Times - Shadow of Heroes) (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - THE WAGER (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - SHADOW OF HEROES (Box 6)
    - Pllblicity Photos - WINTER' S TALE (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - DRUMS OF SNOW (Box 6)
    - MEA Students, 1966 (Box 6)
    - COCK A DOODLE DANDY - proofs (Box 6)
    - ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL - photos & proofs (Box 6)
    - THEATER OF THE CONGRESSIONAL RECORD (Box 6)
    - The Impeachment of President Johnson (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - MOURNING HERCULES (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - BIRTHDAY PARTY (Box 6)
    - Publicity Head Shots (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - Volunteers & Barry (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - WINDOWS & CREDITORS (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - CUCHULAIN (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - VIRTUES OF ADULTERY (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - BLOOD WEDDING (Box 6)
    - TOM PAINE PICTURES (Box 6)
    - THE GOOD WOMAN OF SETZUAN (Box 6)
    - "MEETING PLACE", Oct 19-28, 1967 (Box 6)
    - THE BEGGAR'S OPERA - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - ONCE IN A LIFETIME - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - THE SKIN OF OUR TEETH - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - Publicity Photos - 67-68 Season, 1967-68 (Box 6)
    - THE CHERRY ORCHARD - Photos (Box 6)
    - THE CHAIRS - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - "MEETING PLACE", Contact sheet, 1967 (Box 6)
    - "THE BOOR" (Box 6)
    - VIRGINIA HOLT & CURTAIN (Box 6)
    - "THE CAVERN", 1967-68 (Box 6)
    - UNDERGRADUATE PRODUCTIONS, 1967-68 (Box 6)
    - Lighting Booth & Paul Landry (Box 6)
    - UBU REX (Box 6)
    - "OUT AT SEA" & "SLIGHT ACHE" - Photos (Box 6)
    - CANDAULES, COMMISSIONER (Box 6)
    - THAT SCOUNDREL SCAPIN (Box 6)
    - THE INSPECTOR GENERAL (Box 6)
    - INADMISSIBLE EVIDENCE (Box 6)
    - ANTONY & CLEOPATRA - Color Prints (Box 6)
    - ANTONY & CLEOPATRA - Photos & Proofs (Box 6)
    - PROMETHEUS BOUND - Photos (Box 6)
    - MFA Photos, 1966-67 (Box 6)
    - SRT CANDIDS (Box 6)
    - PHOTOS FILE PRINTS (Box 6)
    - Photos - head shots - miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Graphics (Box 7)
    Contains publicity and advertising and playbills: posters, handbills, programs, mail-outs.
    - (Miscellaneous Posters) (Box 7)
    - Poster Distribution by SRTV's (Box 7)
    - MISC., 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - THE WINTER' S TALE, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - THE DRUMS OF SNOW, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - THE UNKNOWN SOLDIER AND HIS WIFE, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - SHADOW OF HEROES, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - THE CASE, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - ANDROCLES AND THE LION, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - THE WAGER, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - SEASON, 1969-70 (Box 7)
    - TROILUS AND CRESSIDA, Summer 1970 (Box 7)
    - GRAPHICS - SRT, 1965-67 (Box 7)
    - Brochure, 1965-66 (Box 7)
    - Brochure - 1st one, 1966-67 (Box 7)
    - Graphics, 1966-67 (Box 7)
    - Brochure - 2nd one, 1966-67 (Box 7)
    - Poster Distribution by SRTV's (Box 7)
    - Graphics, 1968-69 (Box 7)
    - Graphics, 1965-66 (Box 7)
    - Brochure, 1968-69 (Box 7)
    - Graphics (Volume), 1969-70 (Box 7)
  - Individual Production Notebooks (Box 8)
    Notebooks contain programs and press clippings from productions from each of the five seasons.
    - ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL, 1965-66 (Box 8)
    - THE CHAIRS - THE QUESTIONS, 1965-66 (Box 8)
    - PROMETHEUS BOUND, 1965-66 (Box 8)
    - THE SKIN OF OUR TEETH, 1965-66 (Box 8)
    - THAT SCOUNDREL SCAPIN, 1965-66 (Box 8)
    - A SLIGHT ACHE - OUT AT SEA, 1966-67 (Box 8)
    - ONCE IN A LIFETIME, 1966-67 (Box 8)